<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tech Cafe</string>
    <string name="mission">WELCOME</string>
    <string name="description">Tech Cafe is a platform where you can learn and improve your skills
        within a specific computer science field. Using this app will give you the chance
        to view statistics, common interview questions and practice problems for your chosen field.
        Sign up or Log in to get started!</string>
    <string name="name_title">Tech Cafe</string>
    <string name="signup">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="login">Log In</string>
    <string name="login_logo">Log In</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="button_label_login">Log In</string>
    <color name="beige">#FDF6EC</color>
    <color name="light_brown">#F3E9DD</color>
    <color name="blue">#B7CADB</color>
    <color name="brown">#DAB88B</color>
    <color name="grey">#9D9D9D</color>
    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="enter_information">"Please enter your information"</string>
    <string name="create_new_account">Signing Up</string>
    <string name="email">email</string>
    <string name="Password">Password</string>
    <string name="terms_agreement">\tI have read and agree to the Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login_page">Log In</string>
    <string name="or">OR</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="log_in">Log In</string>
    <string name="google_signin">Google SignIn</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="home_page">Get Started!</string>
    <string name="guest_button">Guest</string>
    <string name="subheader_hp">Click to learn more.</string>
    <string name="sdev">Software Development</string>
    <string name="cs">Cybersecurity</string>
    <string name="ur">UI/UX Research</string>
    <string name="sdDesc">Software development refers to a set of computer science activities dedicated to the process of creating, designing, deploying, and supporting software. Software development can lead to careers in programming, software engineering, and software focussed development. Software development is important because it links and provides new perspectives in the ever-changing world.</string>
    <string name="csDesc">Cybersecurity is the practice of protecting systems, networks, and programs from digital attacks. It refers to the body of technologies, processes, and practices designed to protect networks, devices, programs, and data from attack, damage, or unauthorized access. Cybersecurity is important because organizations collect, process, and store unprecedented amounts of data on computers and other devices.</string>
    <string name="urDesc">UI/UX designing focuses on U - user. The UI aspect focuses on the “user interface” which is essentially the layout of an application. UX focuses on “user experience.” UX works with UI to determine the structure of the interface and the functionality.</string>
</resources>